(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-15T21:12:17.188852",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Agent V7, are you there yet?
Yes, we'll be landing in a bit.
Okay, listen up. This time your mission is to steal a key.
Ya, ya, ya. A key.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. A key.
Hm? A key? What key?
Huh? Jump? What do you mean "jump"?
No... Now?
Hello? Hello?!
Okay, I guess I have to jump now. Here goes nothing.
Three, two, one!
ちゅるり ちゅるり ちゅるり ちゅるり
Chururi, chururi, chururi, chururi
水際 乾いては満ちて
Water's edge, drying and filling up
ちゅるり ちゅるり ちゅるり ちゅるり 胸騒ぎ
Chururi, chururi, chururi, chururi, a premonition
もうきっと潮時よ 顔と名前の貸借
It's time to settle debts of face and name
足を洗うべきよ 媚と恨みの売買
Time to wash my hands of flattery and grudges
目尻の真相は 語るまじ世の煩い
Speak not ofytahthe truth in the corners of my eyes
涙は見せないで 気まぐれ
Don't show your tears, whim
当然の報いだよ 仇と利息の返済
It's just deserts, repayment of vengeance
手を染めた罰よ 恩と喧嘩の売買
Punishment for getting involved, trading fights
裏切りの衝動は 秋の夜の恋煩い
The urge to betray is an autumn lovesickness
項で問わないで さようなら淫ら
Don't ask at the nape, farewell, lewdness
浮かべるか沈むか 暗黙のTOKYO港湾
Floating or sinking, taciturn Tokyo port
ずらからにゃパクられてまうわ 青息吐息
If I don't run, I'll get caught, gasping
笑顔がまぶしいね 見おさめ小雨
That smile is dazzling, a parting drizzle
泡沫を嚼んじゃえば 泡沫を吹き出す大博打思惑師
Spit out bubbles, high-stakes gambler
赤プリがもぬけなら 名ばかりの紀尾井町
If Akasaka Prince is empty, just Kioicho
終わりゆく時代へ 投げろキス 毎度あり型通り
Throw a kiss to the ending era, routine
あの八番出口もヨウナシね… 溜池山王
That Exit 8 is useless too... Tameike-Sanno
ちゅるり ちゅるり ちゅるり ちゅるり
Chururi, chururi, chururi, chururi
水際 乾いては満ちて
Water's edge, drying and filling up
ちゅるり ちゅるり ちゅるり ちゅるり 胸騒ぎ
Chururi, chururi, chururi, chururi, a premonition
笑顔がまぶしいね 見おさめ小雨
That smile is dazzling, a parting drizzle
泡沫を吹っちゃ泡沫を吹かす 大博打思惑師
Blowing bubbles, letting bubbles burst—what a high-stakes speculator!
赤フリがもぬけならば 名ばかりの紀尾井町
If the red-light district is empty, then Kioicho is just a name!
終わりゆく時代へ投げキス 毎度あり型通り
Blow a kiss to the fading era—business as usual, as always!
あの八番出口もヨウナシね…溜池山王
That Exit 8 is useless too... Tameike-sanno.
みずぎわ乾いては満ちて
The water's edge dries and fills,
胸騒ぎ
setting my heart on edge.
みずぎわ乾いては満ちて
The water's edge dries and fills,
胸騒ぎ
setting my heart on edge.
Yeah!
Hello everyone! Welcome
to my 3D showcase!
But before we get further,
if you see here, oops, here...
Here's the hashtag if you want
to use it to tweet or share anything!
Yeah! How was it?
今夜は騒ぎ
Tonight was quite a ruckus!
Oh, there's also Baso!
If you guys are always wondering
where Baso 3D is... here it is!
Yay! So cute, Baso! Aw!
Okay, so now I want to show off
my outfit, I guess. Don't you want to see?
Kalian mau lihat gak sih?
You guys wanna see, right?
Hati-hati biar gak nendang kameramen!
Careful not to kick the cameraman!
Ooh! Maybe I should do a twirl.
Tada! Yeah, okay.
And then my thighs, futomomo!
Yay! Thigh highs! Yeah, thigh highs!
And then the skirt, and then the lock.
Why are we speaking of lock?
Where's the... where's the key?
どこに鍵やこまねた tadi... hmm...
Where did I put it earlier... hmm...
I guess if you guys don't know, we're on the mission... Wa! Lock!
I guess if you guys don't know, we're on a mission... Wait, lock!
Zekatary! Zekatary! Zekatary!
Secretary! Secretary! Secretary!
Kagi motteru jan! Zekatary!
You have the key! Secretary!
Kimi no key! Hurry up! Hurry up!
Your key! Hurry up! Hurry up!
Kimi no key! Zekatary! Hurry up!
Your key! Secretary! Hurry up!
No, no, no! Wait, Baso, hurry up, let's go, let's take the key!
No, no, no! Wait, Baso, hurry up, let's go get the key!
Yay! We finally arrive!
So where's the key?
Where's the key, Buzzel?
Tell me, where's the keyyy?
Buzzel, can you think of where the key is?
Okay, Buzzel doesn't think.
Buzzel juga enggak ikutan, dia enggak tau kuncinya di mana.
Buzzel isn't joining either, he doesn't know where the key is.
Okay.
Um... What?
Ini pintu?
This is a door?
Lah?
Huh?
Bentar, bentar, bentar.
Wait, wait, wait.
Ini ini surga, sih?
Is this... paradise?
Kok, kocak, sih? Kocak banget, laser?
Why is this so funny? Hilarious, laser?
That's crazy.
What the heck? Why would a laser be here?
Okay, you know what? I I get it. It's like security and all that.
Okay, you know what? I get it. It's like security and all that.
Okay, it's security.
It's okay, I've been through this.
I'm the master of infiltration.
I'm literally the best secret agent in the world.
I can do this. Buzzel, can you do it?
Ya, Buzzel, Buzzel, you know... Buzzel probably can't do it. I'll show you how to do it.
Yeah, Buzzel, you know... Buzzel probably can't do it. I'll show you how to do it.
You know what? But I don't know if the key is even the... uh...
Oi! Eh!
Oi! Hey!
Itu Zeta? Itu Zeta? Itu Zeta kah? Oh iya, itu Zeta.
Is that Zeta? Is that Zeta? Is that Zeta? Oh yeah, that's Zeta.
Ah! Zeta! Come on, no!
Lah, malah kabur, dong!
Huh, she's running away instead!
Tunggu, bentar. Kabur? Gimana? Terus- terus gimana? Terus gimana kalau dia kabur?
Wait, hold on. Running away? How? Then what? What if she runs away?
Terus gimana kalau misalnya dia kabur? Buzzel, kamu enggak mau duluan?
Then what if she runs away? Buzzel, you don't want to go first?
Buzzel, kejar! Buzzel, kejar! Go! Go! She's after him.
Buzzel, chase! Buzzel, chase! Go! Go! Chase after him.
You can do it!
Hey, isn't that cheating? He's just like going straight.
Hey, isn't that cheating? He's just going straight.
That's cheating!
Hey, yo, that's cheating.
Lucu, ya?
Funny, huh?
That's cheating!
He just went straight.
Now what? Now what? Now I'm left alone. Okay, it's okay.
I can do this. Mhm.
For the sake of my mission, I shall show to you what a secret agent is truly like.
Duh, gelebiran rangkak dulu enggak, sih? Maybe we can crawl under here.
Ugh, should we crawl first? Maybe we can crawl under here.
Maybe it'll work if I crawl under.
Duh, kena gesek, dikit.
Ugh, got grazed a little.
Tapi bohong, enggak sakit.
Just kidding, it doesn't hurt.
It doesn't hurt, but... um... Okay, that's because of my hair buns.
Or my ears, or whatever you call it.
Okay, what about what if I step over?
If I step over, maybe...
Tidak, itu enggak sakit.
No, that hurts.
Okay, enggak tau, aku udah, enggak bisa ini, capek.
Okay, I don't know, I can't do this anymore, I'm tired.
Capek aku. Kalian komen apa kek, kasih, deh, kasih give me ideas on how I should cross this one then.
I'm tired. You guys comment something, give me ideas on how I should cross this one then.
Ah, you guys can comment.
But, oh, you know what? I I just thought of something.
But, oh, you know what? I just thought of something.
Kenapa enggak ini aja?
Why not just this?
Ini aja enggak sih, guys?
Why not just do this, guys?
Kayak enggak aja enggak sih? Kayak dari 3 2 1
Like, isn't it? Like from 3, 2, 1...
Aduh, enggak bisa.
Ah, can't do it.
Wah, ini bisa, sih. Ini kayaknya bisa, deh.
Whoa, this can work. This looks like it can work.
If I do if I do bridge like this, I can crawl-- Oh. Did Did is it just me or did the laser just went up?
If I do a bridge like this, I can crawl-- Oh. Did it—is it just me or did the laser just go up?
Somebody's operating it. Okay. Well, okay, this is easy.
Limbo! We just have to do limbo, right?
Limbo! Ah, tidak kena!
Limbo! Ah, didn't get hit!
Okay, okay. What did I do? Hey, can't get up, can't get up. Yo.
He just have to crawl. Look at that was stupid.
He just had to crawl. Look at that, was stupid.
That was stupid. Cuz you just you said that and then and then that happened.
That was stupid. Because you just said that and then that happened.
Duh, duh. Okay. Okay.
Ah, ah, ah, just keep crawling, I guess. If I keep crawling, maybe I'll reach the destination faster.
Uh, what about this one? What about this one? Ah, aduh, ini tuh enggak bisa tembus tembok aja ya?
Uh, what about this one? What about this one? Ah, man, why can't I just clip through the wall?
Capek, serius! Aduh kena, kena! Rambutku kena!
I'm tired, seriously! Ah, got hit, got hit! My hair got hit!
Okay. Watch me crawl again.
Watch this, watch this. Watch this, chat. Watch, watch, ta-da-da-da-da-da-da.
Let's go! Ah, da, ah, ah, ah.
Okay.
Hah. Yeah.
Yeah! Ah! Yeah!
Sorry.
O-shiri too big!
My butt's too big!
Okay, yay!
Woohoo! Yay!
Yatta! That was so easy.
Yay! That was so easy.
That was so easy, see?
I'm literally the best agent out there.
Easy, gampang itu mah.
Easy, that's a breeze.
Gampang!
So easy!
Ini apaan? Ini curang nggak sih?
What is this? Isn't this cheating?
Ini tuh kaya... apa sih? Kaya main game, terus level boss-nya tiba-tiba muncul di akhir.
This is like... what is it? Like playing a game and the boss suddenly appears at the end.
Cause... Okay, whatever.
There's like a new... There's like a new...
What? And it's moving!
This is so unfair.
Bisa disuri nggak?
Can I sneak past?
I don't know if I can make it.
Put your bets if I can... if you guys think I can make it.
Place your bets on whether I can... if you guys think I can make it.
Three!
Two!
Wah, tapi bawa...
Wah, but bring...
Three!
Two!
One! Woo!
Yay! Yatta!
Yay! We did it!
Let's go! Let's go, we made it!
Bazo, bazolah, bazo...
Bazo, Bazo...
Bazo... bazo udah kabur. Bazo nggak ada. Ya udahlah.
Bazo... Bazo already ran away. Bazo's not here. Oh well.
Ya udah, ayo sekarang kita kejar sekretaris. Ayo cepat! Cepat, cepat, cepat!
Alright, let's chase after Secretary now. Come on, quick! Quick, quick, quick!
Ayo, kejar.
Come on, chase!
I gotta find the key.
Wah! Wah!
Whoa! Whoa!
Ini ruangan apaan? Aneh banget sumpah.
What kind of room is this? It's so weird, I swear!
This is such a weird room. Where's the key?
Ah... Ada Bazo sama Sekretaris.
Ah... There's Bazo and Secretary.
The key! Kagi motteru.
The key! They have it.
Bazo! Chodai! Eh? Eh? Terbang?
Bazo! Give it to me! Huh? Huh? Flying?
Wah! Come on! Kedalam...
Wah! Come on! Inside...
Kagi ga naka ni iru? Miskas de? Are? Eh?
Is the key inside? Maybe? Huh? Eh?
Sekretaris! Kasih tau! Kasih tau!
Secretary! Tell me! Tell me!
Ini gimana, ini gimana harus ngapain aku? Ah... Ah...
What is this, what am I supposed to do? Ah... Ah...
I see, I see. Okay, okay. So, somebody has to press the button, right?
Okay, okay. Wagatta.
Okay, okay. Got it.
I get it now. Okay, okay.
Uhh... Dareka inai kana?
Uhh... Is anyone here?
Dareka tasukete! Tasukete!
Somebody help! Help!
Tasukete dotta no? Dare ga... zettai!
Help? Who... definitely!
Zeta! Ah, ah, dare ga kita.
Zeta! Ah, ah, someone came.
O-meru-poru-chan! Ah, kasu-senpai!
Oh, Meru-Poru-chan! Ah, Kasu-senpai!
Doshita no? Doshita samui no? Doshita no?
What's wrong? Are you cold? What's wrong?
Doshitano? Eh, doko, doko? Doshitano?
What's wrong? Eh, where, where? What's wrong?
Kagi, kagi wa naka ni iru. Ja, koko... lock, ban! Te iu koto de?
The key, the key is inside. So, here... lock, boom! Like that?
Dame, dame, dame, dame.
No, no, no, no.
Kowashicha dame! Don't, don't, don't destroy it! No, no, no, no, no!
Don't break it! Don't, don't, don't destroy it! No, no, no, no, no!
Why? Why, why, why not? Why? Why? Why? Why?
Doshitena... Na, Poka-senpai... Batton... oshite kudasai.
What is it... Hey, Polka-senpai... please press the button.
Ja, futari de issho ni kyoryoku shite, koete, etto, dosho? Are... no naka ni Zeta ga kote wiii...
Well, the two of us cooperate together, overcome it, um, what should we do? Ah... Zeta is inside that... wii...
De, saki no... soso, soso, soso, kagi me... Soso, soso, soso, soso toru kara.
And, the previous... right, right, right, get the key... right, right, right, right, I'll get it.
Ja, Porka ga koko de botan osu kara.
Then, Polka will press the button here.
Hai. Hai. Hai. Ja, Zeta wa mo soko de wiiii... de saritoki de.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Well, Zeta is right there wiiii... and when leaving.
Un, un. Ganbaru kara. Makaseru. Makaseru. Ganbaru!
Yeah, yeah. I'll do my best. Leave it to me. Leave it to me. I'll do my best!
Makaseru. Sekretaris use please so... Makaseru. Arigatou.
Leave it to me. Secretary, use please so... Leave it to me. Thank you.
Arigatou. Ja, itterasshai.
Thank you. Well, have a safe trip.
Arigatou. Um... Kaette... senaka kanarazu...
Thank you. Um... Return... definitely back...
O... O... O... Zeta-chan! Zeta-chan!
Oh... Oh... Oh... Zeta-chan! Zeta-chan!
Sonna koto ni nacchatte kedo, daijoubu? Zeta?
Things turned out like this, but are you okay, Zeta?
Kita! Poka-senpai!
You came! Polka-senpai!
Tasukete! Tasukete!
Help! Help!
Tasukete ja nai yo! Sou, Bazo mo... you must go there! Zeta mo tasukete, Bazo mo tasukenai to ikenai no? Polka wa!
Not help! That's right, Bazo too... you must go there! Do I have to save Zeta and Bazo too, Polka?
Tasukete!
Help!
Kagi sagashi ni iku zo! Un, un, un, un, ja Polka ga kono botan noru kara, oshite, dono hen ka?
I'm going to look for the key! Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, well Polka will step on this button, so press it, where abouts?
Ano, ne... ah, sore... taihen sou da na. Iku yo!
Um... well, ah, that... sounds tough. Let's go!
Ja, migi kara...
Well, from the right...
Uwa! Uwa, taihen sou da na.
Whoa! Whoa, that sounds tough.
Takai no heiki, chinami ni. Takai no kowaku nai?
Heights are fine, by the way. Aren't heights scary?
Iya, kowaku nai. Zenzen kowaku... Ja, koko da! Hai, start! Yatta!
No, not scary. Not scary at all... Well, here! Yes, start! Yay!
キャー！
Waaah!
離れる！
It's moving away!
あー！
Ah!
左！左！左！左！
Left! Left! Left! Left!
ちょっと無理です、あの
It's impossible, um...
動かないです、こんな
it won't move like this.
さすがに！器用に動かないじゃん！
Seriously! It doesn't move smoothly at all!
どこが、どこ辺そう？どこ辺そう？
Where, around where is it?
見えた？
Did you see it?
うん。
Yeah.
あ、見えた？
Oh, you see it?
これ？
This?
あ！あ！あ！
Ah! Ah! Ah!
なんかこれ、鍵持ってないかな。鍵どこ？
I wonder if this has the key. Where's the key?
There's no key!
それね、多分外れだ。
That one is probably a miss.
外れ？
A miss?
それは多分普通のワズだわ。
Yeah, that's probably just a regular Wazu.
でも普通のワズも可愛いからね、こっちもね、ね。
But regular Wazu is cute too, right here.
あ、あ、あ、そんなに雑に投げられてさ、かわいそうに。
Ah, being thrown so carelessly, poor thing.
もう一回帰ろう。オッケー。
Let's go back again. Okay.
大丈夫、大丈夫、オッケー、オッケー。
It's alright, okay, okay.
大丈夫、そろそろあのなんかそこってさ、どんな感じ？
It's fine. By the way, what's it like up there?
高い、怖い？
Is it high? Scary?
うん、怖くない。
Yeah, not scary.
怖くない。
Not scary.
怖くない！怖くない！跳ね返した方がいいね！怖くない！
Not scary! Not scary! Better bounce back! Not scary!
じゃもう一回探そうね！怖くない！怖くない！
Let's search again! Not scary! Not scary!
はい、はい！
Yes, yes!
さあどうする？
Now, what should we do?
どこだ？どこ辺？あと何秒？
Where is it? Which area? How many seconds left?
さあ、どこへ？あ、見た？見た？
Now, where? Oh, did you see it?
見えた！
I saw it!
見えた！見えた見えた見えた！真ん中よ！ヘイ、ストップ！
I saw it! Right in the middle! Hey, stop!
オッケー、オッケー、オッケー、オッケー！
Okay, okay, okay, okay!
どうか？
How is it?
これはさすがに行ったんじゃない？
Didn't this actually get it?
ここじゃないかも。
Maybe this isn't it.
嘘でしょ？
No way.
ここじゃないかも。
Maybe this isn't it.
ねえ、ポーカーゼータ、ここじゃないかも！
Hey, Polka Zeta, maybe this isn't it!
いや、まだわかんない。み、み、な、な、な、うーん。
No, we don't know yet. Se-se-see... hmm.
え？あ！あ！
Eh? Ah! Ah!
あ！
Ah!
ああー！
Waaah!
何やってるの！やばいってそれ！
What are you doing! That's dangerous!
それは！それは！
That is! That is!
え？大丈夫？
Eh? Are you okay?
焦げた？
Did you get scorched?
あれ？
Huh?
大丈夫？
You okay?
大丈夫じゃないかも。
Maybe I'm not okay.
繊維切れてないかな？大丈夫かな？
I wonder if the fibers are cut? Is she okay?
いやまあ、そういう時のためにね、あのホロライブはね、いつもね、こうやって頑張ってますから。大丈夫ですよ、ゼータさんはこうやって無事です。
Well, for times like these, Hololife always works hard like this. It's fine, Zeta is safe like this.
いや、私無事じゃないよ。
No, I am not safe at all!
え、無事じゃないの？
Eh, you're not safe?
無事じゃないよ！
I'm not safe!
じゃ、なんとかして早く無事を確かめなくちゃ。
Then we better hurry and check if you're okay somehow.
まあでもよかった、黒焦げだけで済んで。よかったよかった。じゃあ行くよ、ゼータ。
Well, I'm glad it was just charred. Good, good. Let's go, Zeta.
オッケー、もうちょっとだよ。頑張って探して！じゃ、本気で探して！オッケー、オッケー。
Okay, just a bit more. Search hard! Seriously search! Okay, okay.
うん。みんなも頑張ってって！ゼータ頑張れって！コメントして！オッケー、オッケー、オッケー！
Yeah. Everyone, cheer for her! Comment that Zeta can do it! Okay, okay, okay!
そういうこと。Cheer for me!
That's right. Cheer for me!
オッケー！シャモニーオッケー！じゃあいくぞ、せーの！
Okay! Chamony okay! Let's go, ready, go!
おら！
Ora!
おお！
Oooh!
お、どう？ちょっと？
Oh, how is it? A bit?
ちょっと、ちょっと、ちょ、ちょっと右かも！ちょっと右かも！
A bit, a bit, maybe a bit to the right!
ジャストップ、はい！
Just stop, right there!
いや、あー！あー！オッケーオッケーオッケーオッケー。
No, aaah! Okay, okay, okay, okay.
あ、見える、見える。頑張って越えて、ふう、ふう言ってるわ、取れないそれ。
Ah, I can see it. Panting hard, can't reach that.
見える見える見える、見えてきた？うんうん見える見える見える。
I can see it! Can you see it? Yeah, I can see it.
これじゃない？あ、取れた！
Isn't this it? Ah, I got it!
え、それ！それ！正解！正解！正解のことです、それは！おー！
Eh, that! That! Correct! That's the correct one! Ooh!
いい眺めだな。これ合ってるかな？
What a nice view. Is this right?
それ、合ってますよゼータさん。それ、合ってます！おめでとう！
That's right, Zeta. That's correct! Congratulations!
やっと！あ、落ちてきた！
Finally! Ah, it's falling down!
よかった！これ鍵だよ！
Great! This is the key!
ゼータ、早く降りてこないとゼータが今度大変なことになっちゃうから、下ろしてあげなきゃ。
Zeta, if you don't come down soon, you'll be in big trouble, so I have to let you down.
そうか、今待ってるゼータ！
That's right! Zeta, waiting for you now!
ゼーターーー！
Zetaaaaa!
おお、すごい、すごい！ゼータ！ほら、見ててくる、見ててくる。見てて見てて見てて。
Oh, amazing, amazing! Zeta! Look, look here. Watch, watch, watch.
見てて。
Watch this.
あ！ほら、できた！かわいい！やった！感動の再会！
Ah! Look, I did it! Cute! Yay! A touching reunion!
あ、ぎゅってしてあげてよ。あ、はいはいはいはい。ぎゅってね。
Give her a hug. Ah, yes, yes, yes. A hug.
死にを？
Shi-ni-wo?
え？死にゼネ？
Eh? Shinizene?
まだ死に、かしこっちじゃん！死にゼネ？君のキー？君のキー？君のキー？
Still shi-ni, you're smart! Shinizene? Your key? Your key? Your key?
ポコポコなぐってを今！
You were punching her just now!
鍵ちょうだい。
Give me the key.
ポコポコ殴ってたよ今！
You were punching her repeatedly just now!
あ、鍵もらった？大丈夫？もらった！よかった！
Ah, did you get the key? Are you okay? Got it! Great!
じゃあね。
See ya.
え？じゃあね。
Eh? See ya.
じゃあ、こっち鍵もらったよ！おめでとう！
Well, I got the key here! Congratulations!
いいよ、いいよ。なんか殴られてたとき？いやいや、大丈夫！
It's fine. What, when I was getting punched? No, no, it's fine!
大丈夫。あれがね、あれがいいんだ。あれが求められてるものらしいです。
It's fine. That's good. That seems to be what was needed.
よかったね。おめでとう！頑張った甲斐があった！
I'm glad. Congratulations! Your hard work paid off!
鍵もらったぞ！やった！いえーい！
I got the key! Yay! Hurray!
じゃあ、もしかしてポルカさ、頑張ったからさ、何かくれないかな？
So, since Polka worked hard, won't you give me something?
えー！？えー！？えー！？えー！？
Ehー!? Ehー!? Ehー!? Ehー!?
うーん、じゃあ
Hmm, well then...
これあげるかな。くれるのかな？何くれるんだろ？はい、なんだろう？
I wonder if I should give you this. Will she give it to me? What will she give me? Yes, what could it be?
あ、しっぽかわいい！しっぽかわいい！急に触るのやめて！
Ah, your tail is cute! Stop touching it so suddenly!
オッケー！たーん！え、なになにこれ？
Okay! Ta-da! Eh, what is this?
ZETAMIN！ゼタミン！ゼタミン！
ZETAMIN! Zeta-Min! Zeta-Min!
これは何？飲む？と、どうなる？
What is this? Drink it? What happens then?
これなんだら、If you drink this, 200 IQ! 200 IQ! 200 IQ!
If you drink this, 200 IQ! 200 IQ! 200 IQ!
IQ200！ゼータのようになれちゃう？うん、ゼータ。
200 IQ! Can you become like Zeta? Yeah, Zeta.
ゼータ、ゼータ！これでゲットできた！
Zeta, Zeta! We got it with this!
もゲットできたもんね。
You got it too, right?
うん。
Yeah.
これでじゃあ、Zetaはじゃあもう次の部屋に行けるってこと?
With this, does that mean Zeta can go to the next room?
うん。
Yeah.
よかった！おめでとう！
Yay! Congratulations!
ちょっと、これ置くからちょっと二人で写真、写真。
Wait, let me put this down so we can take a picture together.
あ、はいはい。
Oh, sure, sure.
イェーイ！ピース！ピース！イェーイ！
Yay! Peace! Peace! Yay!
Zeta改めて3Dおめでとー！
Zeta, congratulations again on your 3D!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
あ、ちなみに
Oh, by the way...
何？
What?
ちなみに、
By the way...
え？
Eh?
何？
What?
えっと、これは、はい、1万円です。
Um, this is, yes, 10,000 yen.
1万円？
10,000 yen?
100万円。
1 million yen.
100万円？
1 million yen?!
ちょ、どっ、1万円で。
Wait, let's go with 10,000 yen.
1万円で。
For 10,000 yen.
100万円ね。
1 million yen.
1万円で！
For 10,000 yen!
いやあ！じゃあこれ、あ！
Yikes! So this... Ah!
お疲れ様です！
Good work!
マイスター、先輩Zetaのビカ盗まれ…
Meister, Senpai Zeta's vika got stolen...
オッケー、ウェル、オッケー、アイ・スティル・ハブ・ザ・キー。
Okay, well, okay, I still have the key.
Aku masih punya kuncinya, jadi kita bakal pakai kunci ini untuk buka ruangan selanjutnya. I'm gonna use this key for the next room.
I still have the key, so we're gonna use it to open the next room. I'm gonna use this key for the next room.
オッケー、レッツゴー！レッツゴー！
Okay, let's go! Let's go!
うわー！
Woah!
うわー！Finally, now that we got the key,
Woah! Finally, now that we got the key,
we unlocked this new room!
うーん。
Hmm.
鍵、ここはどこ？真っ赤だな、ここ。
The key, where is this? It's so red here.
ここ…、ちょっと、あ、楽器色々ある。うわー！うわー！
Here... Wait, ah, all kinds of instruments. Woah! Woah!
It's also really like wide, heroing it.
It's also really wide, huge!
うわー！What kind of place do you guys think this is? Hmm?
Woah! What kind of place do you guys think this is? Hmm?
Band?
No, no, no, no, no. Emang boleh selucu ini? Ya bolehlah.
No, no, no, no, no. Is it allowed to be this cute? Of course it is.
A music room? No, no, no, no, no.
Well, kind of. It's actually a jazz club!
Wow! Isn't that so cool?
Wait, where did Botan and Lamy go?
Did they?
あれ？
Huh?
ミニチェロかん？
Mini cello?
ここに、あ、これ、ドラム。うーん、drums、I see.
Here, ah, this, drums. Hmm, drums, I see.
Drum roll.
お、What's this? What's this?
Oh, what's this? What's this?
お、Electric guitar! じゃん！
Oh, electric guitar! Ta-da!
お、お、What about, what about this? It's a piano! But,
Oh, what about, what about this? It's a piano! But,
あれ？
Huh?
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. I see something over there. あれ？
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. I see something over there. Huh?
それ、猫じゃない？
Isn't that a cat?
あー！It's a kitty! It's actually a cat! That's so cute!
Ah! It's a kitty! It's actually a cat! That's so cute!
ぎゅぎゅぎゅぎゅぎゅぎゅぎゅぎゅぎゅ
Gyu-gyu-gyu-gyu...
あ、バランにがレスポンス。きみ、きみは上品。
Ah, Balan ni, no response. You, you're not polite.
Okay! Well, look at this beautiful, beautiful piano! Hmm.
Should I, should I sit on it?
Hmm, should I sit on it?
What do you guys think? I'm just going to take a seat.
うわー！ Bow down before me, peasants!
Woah! Bow down before me, peasants!
Bahasa kucing enggak! Cat cafe bukan!
It's not cat language! It's not a cat café!
Ini jazz club, bukan cat cafe.
This is a jazz club, not a cat café.
やあ！ Okay, um,
Yay! Okay, um,
maybe I should, maybe I should play a little bit, or am I, or am I playing? Let's see.
うわー！ Okay. Okay, okay. え、鍵盤が斜め階段たい、thanks.
Woah! Okay. Okay, okay. Eh, the keyboard is diagonal stairs, thanks.
Okay. Hmm. Okay, you know what? Let's play.
やあ！
Yay!
あー！ Piano time, baby!
Ah! Piano time, baby!
あの、マイナ、あ、まりじょき、えんと、るりか
Um, maina, ah, marijoki, endou, rurika
やあ！ Well, you know what? Since this is such a beautiful stage and all
Yay! Well, you know what? Since this is such a beautiful stage and all
with all the instruments here and there, you know what?
Might be a waste if we don't sing here, right? Kaya udah jauh-jauh, buka kunci, masuk jazz club,
Might be a waste if we don't sing here, right? Since we came all this way, unlocked the door, entered the jazz club,
sia-sia dong kalau kita enggak nyanyi.
It'd be a waste if we didn't sing.
Iya enggak?
Right?
Should we sing?
Okay, you know what? Might as well, let's sing!
揺らせ一秒 駆けたら summer girls
Sway for a second, once you run, summer girls
夢への道はストレート
The road to your dreams is straight ahead.
視線 誰にも譲れない
I won't yield my gaze to anyone—
Please, Gaze on Me!
きっと始まる fantastic time
A fantastic time is bound to begin.
ゴールは Spot light
The goal is the spotlight,
I'm the heroine
キミを頂戴
Claiming you for myself.
Please, Gaze on Me!
きっと始まる fantastic time
A fantastic time is bound to begin.
みんな 準備はいいですか？ Burning
Is everyone ready? Burning!
うなづいて 陽炎も Heat up
Nod along, even the heat haze heats up.
どうしよう 上昇 アガる空気
What should I do? The rising air gets higher,
Let's go! さあ太陽 燃えて最高潮
Let's go! Now, sun, burn to the peak!
負けられない 興奮もハートも
Unbeatable, both excitement and my heart—
駆け引きは No no
No playing hard to get, no no.
ゲート開いたなら 一瞬のドラマ
Once the gate opens, it's a momentary drama.
走れ 夏の方へ！
Run toward the summer!
揺らせ一秒 駆けたら summer girls
Sway for a second, once you run, summer girls
夢への道はストレート
The road to your dreams is straight ahead.
視線 誰にも譲れない
I won't yield my gaze to anyone,
Please, Gaze on Me!
きっと沸き立つ fantastic time
A fantastic time is bound to surge.
ゴールは Spot light
The goal is the spotlight,
I'm the heroine
キミを頂戴
Claiming you for myself.
Please, Gaze on Me!
きっと沸き立つ fantastic time
A fantastic time is bound to surge.
絶対 最上 掴みたい Feeling
I definitely want to grab the ultimate feeling.
全身全霊 めぐるから Get hot
Circulating through body and soul, get hot.
テンション高揚 欲しいモノへ
Tension rising, toward what I desire,
今 Ride on time さあ一緒に Show time
Now ride on time, come on, show time together.
ピーク 迎えるとき 遠慮はいらない
When reaching the peak, no need to hold back.
せめぎあい Oh oh
Struggling against each other, oh oh.
Spark 汗とプライド ジレた運命
Spark, sweat and pride, an impatient destiny.
連れて 夏の方へ！
Take us toward the summer!
挑む世界は 魅惑の Sunlight floor
The world we challenge is an enchanting sunlight floor.
天井知らずのボルテージ
Endless voltage.
火照る季節を モノにして
Make this glowing season your own.
Please, Gaze on Me!
クラリさせたい Exciting time
I want to make you dizzy, exciting time.
ゴールは Spot light
The goal is the spotlight,
I'm the heroine
キミを頂戴
Claiming you for myself.
Please, Gaze on Me!
クラリさせたい Exciting time
I want to make you dizzy, exciting time.
関係ない どんな私だって 真夏 駆け出せば Venus
It doesn't matter what kind of me I am, once I run into midsummer, I'm Venus.
アツくなれば一歩で Change & happy
If it gets hot, in one step, change & happy.
眩しすぎる今日を 踊るように手にしよう
Let's take today, which is too dazzling, into our hands like dancing.
さあ Here we go! ビートは止まらない
Now here we go! The beat won't stop.
Keep 思うままに 身を預けて
Keep, surrender your body as you wish.
灼熱へ Go go
To the scorching heat, go go.
Warp 本能のリズム 打ち鳴らして
Warp, beating out the rhythm of instinct.
走れ 夏の方へ！
Run toward the summer!
揺らせ一秒 駆けたら summer girls
Sway for a second, once you run, summer girls
夢への道はストレート
The road to your dreams is straight ahead.
視線 誰にも譲れない
I won't yield my gaze to anyone,
Please, Gaze on Me!
きっと始まる fantastic time
A fantastic time is bound to begin.
ゴールは Spot light
The goal is the spotlight,
I'm the heroine
キミを頂戴
Claiming you for myself.
Please, Gaze on Me!
きっと始まる fantastic time
A fantastic time is bound to begin.
あー 今月で3周年だって！CDおめでとう！
Ah, it's 3 years this month! Congrats on the CD!
ありがとう！来てくれてありがとう！呼んでくれてありがとう！
Thank you! Thanks for coming! Thanks for having us!
ありがとう！ありがとう！
Thank you! Thank you!
いや顔、可愛い でございますし！先パイも可愛いよ！やった！
Well, your face is so cute! Senpai is cute too! Yay!
お互いついに3D一緒！一緒！嬉しいでござる！
Together in 3D at last! Together! I'm so happy!
よーくも可愛いけど、ね、このステージもすごくおしゃれでござるな！
You're cute too, but hey, this stage is also very stylish!
ステージいいね、広いね！おしゃれ！てかさ、あっちの方に何かあるでござるか？
The stage is nice, spacious, stylish! Wait, is there something over there?
じゃあ、案内するよ！案内してくれる？やった！行く行く行く！
Then I'll guide you! Will you guide me? Yay! Let's go!
わあー！すごーい！めちゃくちゃおしゃれでござる！
Whoa! Amazing! It's so stylish!
うわ、これジャズクラブだから
Wow, this is a jazz club,
ちょっとおしゃれだね
so it's pretty stylish!
ね、すごいおしゃれ！
Yeah, super stylish!
ステージがこっちなでことだよね
Oh, the stage is over here, right?
あ、こっちから来たから
Ah, since we came from this way,
おお、すごい！かっこいいね、Zeta！
Oh, wow! So cool, Zeta!
うん、めっちゃかっこいい！
Yeah, super cool!
え、猫もあるよ！
Wait, there's a cat too!
猫？
A cat?
見る？猫見る？
Want to see it? Want to see the cat?
見る見る！
See, see!
キャット
Cat!
あ！
Oh!
猫だ！
It's a cat!
猫！猫！触ってもいい？
Cat! Cat! Can I pet it?
あ、いい、猫
Ah, sure, cat...
猫、猫！猫かわいい！
Cat, cat! Cute cat!
かわいい！猫かわいい！
Cute! Cute cat!
あ、違う！猫じゃない！
Ah, wait, no! Not a cat!
あ、違う、嘘！
Ah, wait, no way!
猫じゃない！
It's not a cat!
え、猫じゃない？猫じゃない？
Wait, not a cat? Not a cat?
Zetanキャット？
Zetan Cat?
の、Zetanにおキャット？
N-no, Zetan's cat?
の、おキャット？
N-no, cat?
これ耳じゃない？
Aren't these ears?
耳じゃないの？
Aren't they ears?
おかしい、おかしい、おかしい、おかしい！ね、猫かわいい！
That's weird, weird, weird, weird! Cute cat!
猫かわいい！
Cute cat!
ゼタンのか？
Zetan's?
猫かわいい！ゼタンのか？
Cute cat! Zetan's?
かわいいね！
So cute!
あ、あと、あと
Oh, also, also...
なんか、えっと、実はね、プレゼントがあって、うんうんうんうん、プレゼントあげる！
Actually, um, I have a present for you! Yep, yep, yep, I'm giving you a present!
え、やった！プレゼント？
Eh, yay! A present?
これ、Zetanビーム！
Here, Zetan Beam!
Zetanビーム！
Zetan Beam!
え？わ、すごい！Zetanビーム！
Eh? Wow, amazing! Zetan Beam!
Zetanビーム、これ飲んだら、ゼタ様が
Zetan Beam! If you drink this, Zeta-sama will...
あの、賢いになる。
um, become smart!
か、賢い、強い、強い！
S-smart, strong, strong!
うん、そうそう、もっと強くなる。
Yeah, exactly, even stronger!
すごい！パワーアップアイテム！
Amazing! A power-up item!
いや、パワーアップアイテム、スペシャルアイテム、スペシャルアイテム！
Yeah, power-up item, special item, special item!
やった！サンキュー！ゼタ、大事にします！
Yay! Thank you! Zeta, I'll cherish it!
はい！
Yes!
ありがとう！大事にするよ。
Thank you! I'll cherish it.
ありがとう！大事にするよ！
Thank you! I'll cherish it!
じゃあ、どうぞ座ってください。
Now, please have a seat.
ありがとう！
Thank you!
じゃあちょっとね、座ろうかな。
Then let's sit down for a bit.
うん、しゃべろう。
Yeah, let's chat.
そうそうそう、座ろう。
That's right, let's sit.
はあ、すごい。いつもとてもいい感じでございますね。
Ah, amazing. It's always such a nice vibe.
ねえ、ふわふわ～
Yeah, so fluffy~
ねえ、改めて今日は呼んでくれてありがとうございますでございます！
Say, thank you so much for inviting me today!
いやー、こちらこそありがとう！
No, no, thank you so much!
ねえ、なんで今日はさ、風真のこと呼んでくれたの？
Say, why did you invite Kazama today?
え、好きだから！
Eh, because I like you!
え、そんな、そんなストレートに……
Eh, such— such a straight answer...
照れちゃったの！
I got all embarrassed!
うれしい！
I'm so happy!
え、コラボ……
Uh, collab...
なんかしたも、えっと、なんだっけ、あ、確か何回か、てかいっぱい……結構ライ感の……
Did we collab? Um, what was it, ah, I'm sure a few times, or rather a lot... quite a few times...
そうそうそうそうそう、コラボしてって、なんか、まあ、とにかく好きになっちゃって、
That's right, right, right, we collabed, and somehow, well, anyway, I ended up liking you so much,
好きになっちゃって……
ended up liking you so much...
うれしでございます。
I am so happy.
で呼んでくれたんだ今日。そうそうそうそう。ありがとう！
And you invited me today. That's right, that's right. Thank you!
で、今日ね、一緒に歌わせていただいた曲が「Gaze on Me」っていう曲で、
And today, the song we sang together is called "Gaze on Me,"
その、風真も、あの、先々先輩の3Dライブで知ったんだけど、ゼタも、先々先輩の3Dライブで知んだんだっけね？そうそう。
and Kazama, um, learned about it from the senpai's 3D live, and Zeta, you also learned about it from the senpai's 3D live, right? Yeah, yeah.
ってことあって、そう、ってことで、
That happened, so, yeah, because of that,
ねえ、この曲を一緒に歌わせていただい、楽しかった！一緒に歌えて楽しかったでございます！
hey, singing this song together, it was fun! I'm so glad we could sing it together and have fun!
いやあ、いやあ、曲はね、「Gaze on Me」
Yeah, yeah, the song, "Gaze on Me,"
「Gaze on Me」曲が本当に好きなので、
I really love the song "Gaze on Me,"
なんかお二人で一緒に踊りたい！
so like, I want the two of us to dance together!
歌いたいし！
And sing together!
だから選んだ！
That's why I chose it!
はあ、呼んでくれたんだ！風真のこと、風真のこと選んでくれたってこと！
Ah, you invited me! You chose Kazama, you chose Kazama!
うん！あーうれしい！ありがとう！でも本当にね、一緒に歌って踊れてすごく楽しかったでございます！
Yeah! Ah, I'm so happy! Thank you! But really, singing and dancing together was so much fun!
ねえ、風真、これからもね、ゼタと一緒に歌ったり踊ったり、
Hey, Kazama, from now on too, singing and dancing with Zeta,
ね、せっかく3Dにゼタだから、
hey, since Zeta is finally in 3D,
一緒にやりたいなって思うんだけど、ゼタはどうですか？
I'd love to do it together, what do you think, Zeta?
え、一緒にダンスしたい！一緒にやりたい！
Eh, I want to dance together! I want to do it together!
本当に？ほんとだね、じゃあこれからもいっぱいに一緒に歌って踊ってやろうね！
Really? Really, then from now on let's sing and dance together a lot more!
いやー、やったー！
Yay!
ね、またさっきの、さっきの、またやろうね！これからの曲もやりましょう！
Hey, let's do that part from earlier again! Let's do other songs too!
はっとはっと
Hatto hotto!
OK! OK!
じゃあ頑張ってね！応援してます！またね、バーイ！
Well then, do your best! I'm cheering for you! See you, bye-bye!
バーイ！
Bye-bye!
That was EeLoo and Phi!
She was so cute!
But can't go anywhere because we're going to the next song!
But we can't go anywhere because we're going to the next song!
次の曲行くよ！
Let's go to the next song!
ナゾナゾみたいに地球儀を解き明かしたら
If we solve the globe like a riddle,
みんなでどこまでも行けるね
we can go anywhere together!
ワクワクしたいと願いながら過ごしてたよ
I spent my time wishing to be excited.
かなえてくれたのは誰なの？
Who granted my wish?
時間の果てまでBoooon!!
To the end of time, Boooom!!
ワープでループなこの想いは
This feeling of warping and looping
何もかもを巻き込んだ想像で遊ぼう
let's play with imagination that involves everything!
アル晴レタ日ノ事
On a clear day
魔法以上のユカイが
more delightful than magic
限りなく降りそそぐ
endlessly pouring down,
不可能じゃないわ
it's not impossible!
明日また会うときは
When we meet again tomorrow,
笑いながらハミング
laughing and humming,
楽しさを集めよう
let's gather happiness!
カンタンなんだよ こ・ん・な・の
It's easy, like this—
追いかけてね つかまえてみて
chase after it, try to catch it!
大きな夢＆夢 スキでしょ?
With big dreams and a love for dreams, right?
イロイロ予想ができそうでできないミライ
The future seems predictable yet unpredictable,
それでもひとつだけわかるよ
but there's one thing I know.
キラキラ光って 厚い雲の上を飾る
Sparkling stars decorate the thick clouds above,
星たちが希望をくれると
giving us hope.
時間に乗ろウヨBoooon!!
Let's ride on time, whoosh!!
チープでクールな年頃もね
We're at that cheap and cool age,
寂しがっちゃ恥ずかしいよ なンテ言わせて
it's embarrassing to feel lonely, right? Just kidding!
手と手をつないだら
When we hold hands,
向かうトコ無敵でしょ?
we're invincible heading towards our destination!
輝いた瞳には 不可能がないの
In those shining eyes, nothing is impossible!
上だけ見ていると 涙も乾いてしまう
If you only look up, even tears will dry!
変わりたい
I want to change—
ココロから強く思うほど 伝わる
the more strongly I feel it from my heart, the more it's conveyed!
走り出すよ 後ろの人も おいでよ
Let's start running, come on, those behind too!
ドキドキするでしょ Boooon!!
It must be exciting, whoosh!!
ワープでループなこの想いは
This feeling of warping and looping
何もかもを巻き込んだ想像で遊ぼう
let's play with imagination that involves everything!
アル晴レタ日ノ事
On a clear day
魔法以上のユカイが
more delightful than magic
限りなく降りそそぐ
endlessly pouring down,
不可能じゃないわ
it's not impossible!
明日また会うときは
When we meet again tomorrow,
笑いながらハミング
laughing and humming,
楽しさを集めよう
let's gather happiness!
カンタンなんだよ こ・ん・な・の
It's easy, like this—
追いかけてね つかまえてみて
chase after it, try to catch it!
大きな夢＆夢 スキでしょ?
With big dreams and a love for dreams, right?
おっきな夢 夢 スキでしょ？
Yay! I'm so glad that Mumei was here!
Mumei, kawaii katta yo ne!
Mumei was so cute!
Mumei was so cute, it was so much fun singing, singing and dancing with her! It was so much fun, she was so cute!
Mumei was so cute, it was so much fun singing and dancing with her! It was so much fun, she was so cute!
素晴らしいパフォーマンス、ゼータさん。
That was a wonderful performance, Zeta-san.
あ？
Huh?
Wait, who's...
Who's that voice? Is that...
Yagoo?!
こんにちは。
Hello.
Yagoo?! Yagoo?!
What? Why are you here?
I'm a VIP guest.
Huh? Since when?
Actually, I saw...
That's a door. Who's a jazz club manager?
Was open, so I just came in.
It was open, so I just came in.
I have been watching you since the beginning.
Okay, okay
Well well, you know what, since you're already here anyway, do you want to try singing like the song earlier together?
Well, since you're already here anyway, do you want to try singing the song from earlier together?
Oh yeah, sure.
Aku juga mau.
I want to too.
Aku juga mau! Okay, okay.
I want to too! Okay, okay.
Yeah yeah, okay, oh wow, okay.
Look guys, we can finally hear Yago sing! Yay!
Look guys, we can finally hear Yagoo sing! Yay!
Yeah now, if not now then when?
Ya uda ya, Zeta ya.
Yeah, right, Zeta, right?
Lah, malah bukan baju.
Wait, that's not clothes.
Lah?
Huh?
What? Hitokabu?
Nooo!
Nooooo!
Nooo! Yagoo!
Nooooo! Yagoo!
Yagoo, why did you take Yagoo away? That's our VIP guest! Where are you going?
Yagoo's chat-ta yo! Yagoo! Yagoo left!
Yagoo chatted! Yagoo! Yagoo left!
Oh no, but it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Because we can just call more guest, right? We can call more guest.
because we can just call more guests, right? We can call more guests.
Who cares if Yagoo is gone? Ha, guest-to yonde miyou ka.
Who cares if Yagoo is gone? Let's invite some guests.
Moshimoshi, moshimoshi, moshimoshi.
Hello, hello, hello.
Yabai jyanai? (laugh)
Isn't that bad?
Hi! Thank you so much for coming, Koyori-senpai, Ollie-senpai, Reine-senpai, A-chan.
All right. So, the reason why I called you guys is to do the regular old screenshot time.
Alright! So, the reason why I called you guys is to do the regular old screenshot time.
However, we're going to do something different. So, how about the first person go with like an easy pose, okay?
However, we're going to do something different. So, how about the first person does an easy pose, okay?
Jadi, orang pertama posenya easy, level one pose.
So, the first person's pose is easy, level one pose.
And then next person, the pose gets harder each time, okay? Level two, level three, level four, okay?
And then for the next person, the pose gets harder each time, okay? Level two, level three, level four, okay?
Okay? Okay! Okay? Okay! Okay!
So, I trust you guys to give me pose. Sashi-in time day yo, minna! Sashi-in totte!
So, I trust you guys to give me poses. Screenshot time, everyone! Take a screenshot!
Okay, hai. Ja, um, dari yang paling gampang, siapa yang bakal kasih aku paling gampang ya? Uh, Risu-senpai! Risu-senpai! Go, go!
Okay, right. Now, um, starting with the easiest one, who's gonna give me the easiest one? Uh, Risu-senpai! Risu-senpai! Go, go!
Hai, hai! Ayo, poso apa, poso apa?
Hi, hi! Come on, what pose, what pose?
Okay, karena aku, aku, aku baik ya, aku baik. Jadi, sebagai secret engine yang baik nih, kamu harus bisa camouflage.
Okay, since I'm, I'm, I'm nice, yeah, I'm nice. So, as a good secret agent, you need to be able to camouflage.
Camouflage, okay? Camouflage, okay, okay? Jadi, aku mau kamu camouflage jadi T-Rex.
Camouflage, okay? Camouflage, okay, okay? So, I want you to camouflage into a T-Rex.
T-Rex, okay, T-Rex, T-Rex. T-Rex like dinosaur, T-Rex or... Yang tangannya kecil itu loh.
T-Rex, okay, T-Rex, T-Rex. T-Rex like dinosaur, T-Rex or... The one with the tiny hands, you know.
Okay, okay, fine, fine, fine, fine, okay, okay. Gota do it quickly.
Okay, okay, fine, fine, fine, fine. Gotta do it quickly.
Gini, kepalanya ke belakang ya? Hah? Iya, kepalanya ke belakang.
Like this, head to the back, right? Huh? Yeah, head to the back.
Udah, ini tuh udah ke belakang. Gini, udah, udah, udah. Ini ngerjain, ini ngerjain Kohai namanya.
Already, this is already to the back. Like this, already, already. This is teasing, this is teasing a kohai.
This is bullying kohai. This is my territory.
This is bullying a kohai. This is my territory.
I'm good, I'm good. I'm good, good. Okay, that's it.
Sanji-in dayo? You know what, ya, sanji-in ne.
Screenshot time, you know? You know what, yeah, screenshot.
I mean that was pretty easy. That was pretty easy. Something like that's too easy, too easy, maybe.
I mean, that was pretty easy. That was pretty easy. Something like that is too easy, too easy, maybe.
Thank you, Risu-senpai! How was that? T-Rex enough for you?
That is so cute, very cute T-Rex.
Okay, thank you! Well, I don't know who, um, who should we go? Koyori-senpai, Ollie-senpai, A-chan.
Okay, what about? Okay, what about Koyori-senpai! Yay! Senpai-chan, Koyori-senpai, terima kasih sudah datang.
Okay, what about? Okay, what about Koyori-senpai! Yay! Senpai-chan, Koyori-senpai, thank you for coming.
Domo arigatou gozaimasu! Thank you very much! Thank you very much!
So good, nanka pose chodai.
So good. Give me a pose.
Okay! I want you to do the pose I promised you before in the Totsumachi.
Woah, okay. Ini gozou, okay, okay, okay. In the totsumachi, totsumachi de yakusoku shita yatsu desu.
Woah, okay. In the totsumachi, it's the one I promised in the totsumachi.
Ah, neko no yatsu? So, neko no yatsu.
Ah, the cat one? That's right, the cat one.
Neko, neko dance.
Cat, cat dance.
Neko survive ring cat dance, okay?
Neko... ikimodoshi-gari, okay?
Neko... breath control, okay?
Neko... Neko dance, okay?
Cat... Cat dance, okay?
Neko dance, okay? Neko dance, okay?
Cat dance, okay? Cat dance, okay?
Koko shiburi ni... Koko shiburi neko dance!
For the first time in a while... First-time-in-a-while cat dance!
Neko dance! Neko dance!
Cat dance! Cat dance!
Neko dance! Kawaii, kawaii, neko dance!
Cat dance! So cute, so cute, cat dance!
Eh, sen- sen nya! Sen nya! Nya-nya!
Um, sen- sen nya! Sen nya! Nya-nya!
Nya-nya! Nya-nya! Nya-nya! Nya-nya!
Nya-nya! Nya-nya! Nya-nya!
Moto! Moto power! Power up! Bom bom power, okay? We need doping, okay?
More! More power! Power up! Bom bom power, okay? We need doping, okay?
And maybe we need... we need something to increase my...
My increase... okay! Wait a minute!
Wa... Waaah! Gulp gulp gulp gulp...
Power! Power up! Power up!
Neko dance, okay? Neko dance, okay?
Cat dance, okay? Cat dance, okay?
Koko shiburi ni... Neko dance! Neko dance!
For the first time in a while... Cat dance! Cat dance!
Tsukareta.
I'm tired.
Kawaii! Arigatou!
So cute! Thank you!
Yoku ganbarimashita. Arigatou!
You worked hard. Thank you!
Arigatou Okayu! Arigatou!
Thank you, Okayu! Thank you!
Thank you! Sugi no...
Thank you! Next...
Neko- neko da giant...
Cat- cat da giant...
Um... Okay, what about... Okayu senpai?!
Me, me, me, yay! Me! I choose you! Hehehe.
Ayo, bisa apa? Yang paling susah.
Come on, what can you do? The hardest one.
Um, okay. But first of all, I heard- I heard you had a gun also.
Oh, I do have a gun, yeah.
Really? I want to see it!
Tadana! Wow! Tadana! Wow!
Ta-da! Wow! Ta-da! Wow!
The pose ready in my head. Kamu kamu jongkok.
The pose is ready in my head. You- you squat.
Okay, jongkok. Mm-hm.
Okay, squat. Mm-hm.
Jongkok gini... Terus salah satu kaki kamu di-selonjorin.
Squat like this... Then stretch one of your legs out.
Gini... Di-selonjorin. Ooh! Ha! Ya, kayak gitu.
Like this... Stretch it out. Ooh! Ha! Yeah, like that.
Terus habis itu, kamu kayak tembak ke bagian atas kirinya kamu gitu, atau enggak bagian belakang kanan kamu gitu.
Then after that, you like shoot towards the upper left part of you, or the back right part of you.
Pa! Fa, fa, fa, fa, fa, fa, fa! Wow! Fa, fa, fa, fa, fa, fa, fa! Like secret agent!
Bang! Bang, bang, bang, bang, bang! Wow! Bang, bang, bang, bang, bang! Like a secret agent!
Okay, this is a little bit tough.
Maybe... maybe we got the other way. Wa! Wa! Wa! Wa! Wa! Wa!
Nggak boleh- nggak boleh madep kalian. Keren set, keren set. Hah, oke.
You can't- you can't face the audience. Cool set, cool set. Ha, okay.
Okay, thank you, Okayu senpai!
Okay, next person. Omae! Thank you for coming, Omae!
Okay, next person. Ame! Thank you for coming, Ame!
Thank you for coming, Omae! Oh my god! Okay, Arigato!
Thank you for coming, Ame! Oh my god! Okay, Arigato!
Okay, Om... Um, give me your... the most difficult pose.
Okay, Am... Um, give me your... the most difficult pose.
Ah, the hardest one. Okay, okay.
You know, as a- as a secret agent, it must be pretty tough to, uh, to balance properly, to find inner peace in little stressful situations.
Yeah, I need you to balance on one foot. Wait, do- do you have anything to put on your head maybe?
I mean, I don't have anything. I only have like- I have like bozzu, or...
I mean, I don't have anything. I only have like- I have like bozu, or...
I mean... I have- I have vegeta, I guess.
Oh! If I drop it, look, look! Ah, so heavy! So cute!
Okay, okay. Let's see if you can balance- balance it right on your head and stand on one foot.
Okay. Okay, on my head and then stay on one foot.
Yeah. Like this? Wait, does it- Yeah, yeah! Wait, this is too easy. It's too easy for you! Hold up, easy! This is not easy at all! I'm falling! No, no, no. We got to up the difficulty! No hands, no hands!
No hands! Okay, wait, wait. Ah, da-da-da! Okay, okay. Yeah, that's three seconds! That's three-second count!
Okay, then. Okay, I hope that counts! That counts! Wait, wait, wait! It's too cute! Fuck!
Are we going to get our Zetamit in the mail for our participation?
Oh, yeah! Oh, of course! We'll give you ours- I'll- I'll deliver the Zetamit in person to you.
Thank you everyone for coming! Kite kurete arigatou!
That was fun! That was so much fun! Dekite so much for the poses! Thank you for coming. Arigatou! Arigatou mama!
That was fun! That was so much fun! Thank you so much for the poses! Thank you for coming. Arigatou! Arigatou mama!
Arigatou mama! Thank you! Tanoshinde ne! Bye-bye! Bye-bye, guys! Bye-bye! Thank you!
We're not- It's not over yet until I say it's over. Blumsosai karna! Aku mau menunjukkan sesuatu, yaitu apa tuh? New merch! New goods!
We're not- It's not over yet until I say it's over. Belum selesai karena aku mau menunjukkan sesuatu, yaitu apa tuh? New merch! New goods!
Let's take a look. Ta-da!
It's a holoh3ro Card Case! Ooh, so cool! It's like a...
holoh3ro Card... um there's like the case and inside is a business card
Ini dia card-nya, holoh3ro business card.
Here is the card, the holoh3ro business card.
Kartu holoshi, designer-nya, designer-nya?
Holoshi's card, the designer, the designer?
I mean who, you know, as a secret agent I'm a professional secret agent so I have to have a business card.
Well, if you want to ping-ping ping-ping, aku mau kasih lihat versi real! Versi 3D!
Well, if you want to ping-ping ping-ping, I want to show you the real version! 3D version!
Ready?
Tada! It's the business card! Look!
Isn't it so cute? Mine is grey.
Waktu aku abub-abubu gitu.
When I was like greyish.
Ee... Ittan no wa grey ni natchatteru kedo, kawaii desho? Isn't it so cute? Would you like to buy this? Aku mau gas, aku juga mau. Nice. So cool!
Um... It turned out grey, but isn't it cute? Isn't it so cute? Would you like to buy this? I want to gas, I want it too. Nice. So cool!
S3-tiga marketing. Nice. Ayo dibeli! Versi real, ya, versi real! Yay!
S3 marketing. Nice. Come on, buy it! Real version, yeah, real version! Yay!
Okay. Biaya... It's going to be on sale after the 3D collab stream on the 28th of October, so yeah.
Okay. It's going to be on sale after the 3D collab stream on the 28th of October, so yeah.
Nanti bakal ada on sale pas holohiro 3D collab, oke?
Later there will be an on sale during the holohiro 3D collab, okay?
Gimana? Gak usah skip ad? Jangan-bu skip ad. Aku mau 10.
How is it? No need to skip ad? Don't skip ad. I want 10.
Hahaha. Mau dong! Kayang! Tadi udah kayang!
Hahaha. I want some! Kayang! I already did kayang earlier!
Oke.
Okay.
Impressive, very nice. Okay, it seems like everyone wants it.
Okay. Well, do you guys want me to continue my 3D more, or do you want this business card more? Hmm, I wonder which one you like more?
Skit? You can't skip!
I have an obligation, okay? To show this. Okay!
Um, I think it's um, time to sing my last song.
You want to know what the song is? You guys probably already know what the song is. Kalian tahu nggak sih, kira-kira? Kayak lagunya tuh apa?
You want to know what the song is? You guys probably already know what the song is. Do you guys roughly know? Like, what's the song?
Ayo apa? Apa? Apa? Lagu apa tuh? Lagu apa? Hello, lagu apa? Let me hear you. Let me hear you. Encore? No no no no.
Ayo apa? Apa? Apa? What song is that? What song? Hello, what song? Let me hear you. Let me hear you. Encore? No no no no.
Yes, original song! Yes! Somebody said original song! Yes! I'm going to be singing my original song, original song! The title is...
You're Mine.
As the city lights come alive
Shadows of the night
Help me spin my web
Got my target there in my sight
He can run and hide
But he can't be saved
Goin' in as I make my move
Smooth as that jazzy groove
While the music's playin'
Lethal with a drink in my hand
I've been working a plan
And it's goin' good
Cheers to all your secrets, your desires
全てを手に入れるまで
Until I have it all...
I won't stop
Don't you hide from me
I can see through your eyes 秘密だって
I can see through your eyes, even your secrets
Locked away でも隠しきれない
Locked away, but still I can't hide it
最強な secret agent
The ultimate secret agent
罠をかければ…
Once I set the trap...
you're mine
I can see through your eyes 何処にいても
I can see through your eyes, no matter where you are
In the dark でも逃げきれない
In the dark, you still can't escape
最強な super power でつかまえる
Catching you with my ultimate super power
Got him all caught up in my web
Every word he's said
Ready for replay
Then I slipped and he knew my hand
Took off and he ran thought he could escape
Cheers to all your secrets your desires
今さら気付いても too late cause I won't stop
Even if you realize now, it's too late 'cause I won't stop
Don't you hide from me
Catch and release? Do you think? そんなヘマはしない 最後に仕留めるのが my style
Catch and release? Do you think? I wouldn't make such a blunder, finishing it off is my style
Let you swim for now but You're すでに mine
Let you swim for now, but you're already mine
Just reel in the line
No matter how far you may run to...
I can see through your eyes
何処にいても
In the dark でも逃げきれない
最強な super power でつかまえる
I can see through your eyes
秘密だって
Locked away でも隠しきれない
最強な secret agent
罠をかければ… You're mine
I can see through your eyes
何処にいても
In the dark でも逃げきれない
最強な super power でつかまえる
Baby you're mine
Run but you can't hide
狙ったら、もう離さない
Baby you're mine
Always one step behind
I'll take my time
'Cause baby you're mine
That was...
That was my first original song, "You're Mine"!
I'm glad you guys enjoyed the song. Did you like the song?
The song is about a secret, a secret agent who's trying to find her target and catch her target, that's why it's called "You're Mine." Yeah.
Oh, wait, I'm tired.
Okay. Well, if you want to see the song jacket,
look over here. Ta-da!
Yeah! Isn't it so cute? Kawaii, right?
Yeah, it's going to be released tonight, actually, tonight. So, be sure to stream "You're Mine," okay?
Watch the MV!
Okay, so I guess that concludes today's mission. I guess.
Eh?
Ada penyusup?
Location?
Chess club?
Ini di hajar lagi?
Wait. Ini di hajar lagi?
What? Apa ini?
La, ada penyusup?
La, kok siapa?
La, kok bisa masuk sini?
Eh, the backyard kan?
La, kok baru tahu sekarang?
I'm dead.
Dari tadi nggak ngecek sisi security?
Oh no.
Dahlah.
Woi, kamu!
Siapa namanya?
Berhenti di situ!
Jangan gerak!
Kita ke lokasi sekarang.
Ah, aku?
Aku? Aku bukan penyusup.
Aku bukan penyusup.
Halo?
Ya, gimana?
Ya udah, aku harus lari sekarang.
I have to, I have to escape now.
I can't, I can't be catch there.
Well, see you.
See you. Bye! Bye!
Secretary, you're the reason why I smile and look forward to tomorrow! Thank you for everything!